[{"answer": "Who's joking", "docId": "South-Park-Casa-Bonita.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You have AIDS", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yes. Three friends. You're not my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Casa-Bonita.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'm gonna take Butters. He invited me to his birthday party last month, so I owe him one", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend ih uh... Weh come on, my friend, who the hell else are you gonna take besides my friend and my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Casa-Bonita.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Butters?! You're gonna take THAT butthole?! Why?", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Butters?! You're gonna take THAT butthole?! Why?", "docId": "South-Park-Casa-Bonita.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I have never been a dick to you", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Casa Bonita! Come on, you guys!  Oh, awesome!!  Come on, you guys! my friend's Cave!  Wow, cliff divers!  More sopapillas, please", "docId": "South-Park-Casa-Bonita.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "No! Noooo!  Casa Bonita! Noooo!  AAAAH!! Oh... Go", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hi my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Casa-Bonita.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What isn't it", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "That's not being nice! That's just putting on a nice sweater", "docId": "South-Park-Casa-Bonita.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I know you don't", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, sure, my friend. ", "docId": "South-Park-Casa-Bonita.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Well, the best thing is not to act nice, my friend. Uh, the best thing is to be genuinely nice", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Hey my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Casa-Bonita.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Well what", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Nope, uh I don't see any...  Oh wait. Oh my God! I see it. I see it! It's a meteor! Oh my God", "docId": "South-Park-Casa-Bonita.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "It is! It is getting clsoer! Oh my God", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No Butters!! If you come up, you'll get infected too! You best wait for the radiatino level to go down. Probably... next week sometime. After Saturday. Ugh..", "docId": "South-Park-Casa-Bonita.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "We can't come down there, or else, we'll contaminate you, Butters. No... we just have to survive the best we can", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "\"Pretty cool", "docId": "South-Park-Casa-Bonita.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "What? Fuck my friend.  Ha ha, ", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I... am going... to Casa... Bonita", "docId": "South-Park-Casa-Bonita.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " Ah! Eh. Nuh!  Less than a minute! Less than a minute! my friend", "qsentId": 26}]